Register to The Benny Goodman Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Band and Combo Arrangements
  - WHAT A LITTLE MOONLIGHT CAN DO Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 30B, Folder 18)
    Score: photocopy (for original see BG no.B67/W3)
  - WHAT DO YOU THINK I AM Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 30B, Folder 19)
    BG No.: B290
  - WHAT DOES IT MATTER Woode, Henri, 1936 (Box 30B, Folder 20)
    BG No.: B299/93
  - WHAT GOES ON HERE IN MY HEART Mundy, Jimmy, 1938 (Box 30B, Folder 21)
    BG No.: B300
  - WHAT HAVE YOU GOT THAT GETS ME Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 30B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: A26/575/113
  - WHAT IS THIS THING CALLED LOVE Gutesha, Bobby, 1958 (Box 30C, Folder 23)
    BG No.: D68/257
  - WHAT IS THIS THING CALLED LOVE, 1959 (Box 30C, Folder 24)
    BG No.: D68
  - WHAT YOU GONNA' DO Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 30C, Folder 25)
    BG No.: 80
    SaxA1 is incomplete.
  - WHAT YOU GONNA' DO (Box 30C, Folder 26)
    Parts labeled "Whatta Ya Gonna' Do!" Clarinet part is a 3 stave condensed score (transposed).
  - WHAT'S NEW Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 30C, Folder 27)
    BG No.: 114/B77/C219
  - WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH ME Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 30C, Folder 28)
    BG No.: A84
  - WHAT'S THE REASON Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 30C, Folder 29)
    BG No.: B31/117
  - WHEN BUDDHA SMILES Henderson, Fletcher (Box 30C, Folder 29A)
    BG No.: B12/W4/10/12
    Key: C flat
    All parts except cl are copies. Clarinet part is a recopy labeled "trans. by Sy Johnson".
  - WHEN DREAMS COME TRUE Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 30C, Folder 30)
    BG No.: A32/48/290
  - WHEN I GROW TO OLD TO DREAM Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 30D, Folder 31)
    BG No.: B305
    Sketch is in waltz time; original arrangement is in 4/4.
  - WHEN I GROW TO OLD TO DREAM Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 30D, Folder 32)
    BG No.: 14A
  - WHEN I GROW TO OLD TO DREAM Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 30D, Folder 33)
    BG No.: 42A
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-3/PGBD
  - WHEN I LOOK BACK (Box 30D, Folder 34)
    BG No.: G40
    Clarinet part is 3 stave condensed score (transposed).
  - WHEN I'M FEELING KINDA BLUE Wilson, Gerald (Box 30D, Folder 35)
  - WHEN I'M OUT WITH YOU Edwards, Teddy, 8/9/1964 (Box 30D, Folder 36)
    BG No.: F125
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/PGBD
  - WHEN MY BABY SMILES AT ME Murphy, Spud, 1934 (Box 30E, Folder 37)
    BG No.: A1/55
  - WHEN THE SHEPHERD LEADS THE SHEEP BACK HOME Thompson, Johnny, 1942 (Box 30E, Folder 38)
    BG No.: B48
  - WHEN THE SUN COMES OUT Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 30E, Folder 39)
    BG No.: C331/39A
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PB
  - WHEN YOU'RE SMILING Reidy, Frank, 1969 (Box 30E, Folder 40)
    BG No.: G116/W6
  - WHEN YOU'RE SMILING Williams, George, 1958 (Box 30E, Folder 41)
    BG No.: B385/193
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGBD/vocals
    Includes separate score for vocals (beginning at m.39). Complete.
  - WHEN YOUR LOVER HAS GONE Jenkins, Gordon, 1976 (Box 30E, Folder 42)
    BG No.: G148
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3(2)4/PGBD
  - WHEN YUBA PLAYS THE RHUMBA ON THE TUBA Mundy, Jimmy, 1939 (Box 31, Folder 01)
    BG No.: B306
  - WHERE DO I GO FROM YOU Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 02)
    BG No.: A29
  - WHERE DO YOU KEEP YOUR HEART Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 31, Folder 03)
    BG No.: B291
  - WHISPERING Shirley, Charlie, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 04)
    BG No.: D429/290
  - WHISTLE BLUES Williams, Mary Lou, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 05)
    BG No.: C314
    Parts: cl/saxAAT7B/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGBD/horn
  - WHISTLE WHILE YOU WORK Mundy, Jimmy, 1938 (Box 31, Folder 06)
    BG No.: A65/99
  - WHO Jackson, James (Box 31, Folder 07)
    BG No.: C278/77
    Parts: saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1/BD
  - WHO, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 08)
    BG No.: B367/108
  - WHO Feller, Sid, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 09)
    BG No.: B367
  - WHO CAN I TURN TO Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    BG No.: C315/56A
    Parts: saxATT(-A2)/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/G
  - WHO CARES Gutesha, Bobby, 1958 (Box 31A, Folder 11)
    BG No.: D60/240
  - WHO KNOWS Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 31A, Folder 12)
    BG No.: B293/27
  - WHO'S SORRY NOW Mundy, Jimmy, 1939 (Box 31A, Folder 13)
    BG No.: C155/39
  - WHY CAN'T I, c.1956 (Box 31A, Folder 14)
    BG No.: D401/181
  - WHY DON'T WE DO THIS MORE OFTEN Valentine, Jerry, 1949 (Box 31A, Folder 15)
    BG No.: B295/247
  - WHY DON'T YOU DO RIGHT, 1942 (Box 31A, Folder 16)
    BG No.: B11/W9
  - WHY DON I T YOU DO RIGHT, 1942 (Box 31A, Folder 17)
    BG No.: D5/62A/28
    Parts: tpt1-4/tbn1-2/B/horn
  - WHY DON'T YOU DO RIGHT, 1942 (Box 31A, Folder 18)
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-2/D
    Note that all 3 "Why Don't You Do Right" arrangements differ slightly.
  - WHY WAS I BORN Lanning, Frank, 1934 (Box 31A, Folder 19)
    BG No.: C317
  - WHY'D YA MAKE ME FALL IN LOVE Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 31A, Folder 20)
    BG No.: B294
  - WILLOW WEEP FOR ME Stegmeyer, Bill, 6/1960 (Box 31A, Folder 21)
    BG No.: D322/50
  - WIND AT MY WINDOW, THE Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 31B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: C154/253
  - WINTER WEATHER Powell, Mel, 1941 (Box 31B, Folder 23)
    BG No.: B222
  - WINTER WEATHER - NEW Powell, Mel, 1942 (Box 31B, Folder 24)
    Score for new ending to other "Winter Weather" (BG no.B222). Begins at rehearsal letter D2.
  - WINTER WONDERLAND Todd, Tommy, 1947 (Box 31B, Folder 25)
    BG No.: A86
  - WISE OLD OWL, THE Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 31B, Folder 26)
    BG No.: B360
  - WITH A SMILE AND A SONG Mundy, Jimmy, 1938 (Box 31B, Folder 27)
    BG No.: B310/69
  - WITH ALL MY HEART Murphy, Spud, 1936 (Box 31B, Folder 28)
    BG No.: 372E/106
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PBD
  - WITH PLENTY OF MONEY AND YOU Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 31B, Folder 29)
    BG No.: B297
  - WITHOUT A SHADOW OF A DOUBT Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 31B, Folder 30)
    BG No.: B296
  - WITHOUT A SONG Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 31B, Folder 31)
    BG No.: B236
  - WIVES AND LOVERS Newsom, Tommy, 6/1964 (Box 31B, Folder 32)
    BG No.: F103
    Parts: cl(4)/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGBD
  - WOLVERINE BLUES Henderson, Fletcher, 1945 (Box 31C, Folder 33)
    BG No.: BlO/W8
    SaxB and tbn3 not indicated in score. Includes an extra set of parts. Score is original; all parts photocopies. Complete.
  - WOLVERINE BLUES Masso, George, 7/26/1973 (Box 31C, Folder 34)
    BG No.: G121
    Parts: -cl/saxT/tpt/tbn/PBDV
  - WRAP YOUR TROUBLES Rawitz, Steve, 1978 (Box 31C, Folder 35)
    BG No.: G133
  - WRAP YOUR TROUBLES IN DREAMS Rowles, Jimmy, 9/1960 (Box 31C, Folder 36)
    BG No.: D339/413
    Vibes part labeled "Red". Complete.
  - WRAP YOUR TROUBLES IN DREAMS Henderson, Fletcher, 1947 (Box 31C, Folder 37)
    BG No.: B369
  - WRAP YOUR TROUBLES IN DREAMS Siravo, George, 1945 (Box 31D, Folder 38)
    BG No.: B3 6 9/ W1 0
  - WRAPPIN' IT UP Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 31D, Folder 39)
    BG No.: W11/7/8/29/13/D7
    1949 recopy. Includes complete set of photocopies.
  - WRAPPIN' IT UP Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 31D, Folder 40)
    BG No.: 164/D7
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/GB
    Cl/saxA1(pg.2)B/tpt1/G are pencil parts added to complete the set; all other parts are in Henderson's hand.
  - YAM, THE Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 31D, Folder 41)
    BG No.: B258
  - YANKEE DOODLE NEVER WENT TO TOWN Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 31D, Folder 42)
    Parts: cl/saxATT(-A2)/tpt1-2/tbn1/PGBD
  - YEARNING FOR LOVE Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 31E, Folder 43)
    BG No.: B311/178
  - YESTERDAY Newsom, Tommy, 10/1965 (Box 31E, Folder 44)
    BG No.: F118
  - YESTERDAY Knight, Peter, 1969 (Box 31E, Folder 45)
    BG No.: G123/Y1
    Sax doubles: Al-flute, A2-cl, T1-cl, T2-oboe, B-bscl. Complete.
  - YOU AND I KNOW Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 31E, Folder 46)
    BG No.: B314
  - YOU AND ME THAT USED TO BE, THE Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 31E, Folder 47)
    BG No.: B259
  - YOU AND THE NIGHT AND THE MUSIC Powell, Mel, 1947 (Box 31E, Folder 48)
    BG No.: 136
  - YOU ARE THE SUNSHINE OF MY LIFE
    See SUNSHINE OF MY LIFE.
  - YOU BETTER GIVE ME LOT'S OF LOVING HONEY Cary, Dick, 1943 (Box 31E, Folder 49)
    BG No.: B316
  - YOU CAN CALL IT SWING Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 31E, Folder 50)
    BG No.: C367/19/112
    Parts: saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGB
  - YOU CAN'T HAVE EVERYTHING Powell, Mel, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 01)
    BG No.: 132
  - YOU CAN'T RUN AWAY FROM LOVE Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 32, Folder 02)
    BG No.: C368/171
  - YOU COULDN'T BE CUTER Feller, Sid, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 03)
    BG No.: B377/244
  - YOU DO SOMETHING TO ME Williams, Mary Lou, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 04)
    BG No.: 112
    Parts: cl2/saxT/PG
  - YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT LOVE IS Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 32, Folder 05)
    BG No.: B191
  - YOU GO TO MY HEAD Powell, Mel, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 06)
    BG No.: 133
  - YOU GO TO MY HEAD, c.1945 (Box 32, Folder 07)
    BG No.: C369/57
    Includes photocopy of sheet music with lyrics.
  - YOU GROW SWEETER AS THE YEARS GO BY Mundy, Jimmy, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 08)
    BG No.: B319
  - YOU HIT THE SPOT Williams, George, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 09)
    BG No.: A12/212
  - YOU LUCKY PEOPLE YOU Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    BG No.: A214
  - YOU MUST HAVE BEEN A BEAUTIFUL BABY Mundy, Jimmy, 1938 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - YOU STARTED ME DREAMING Woode, Henri, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    BG No.: B322
  - YOU TOOK ADVANTAGE OF ME (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - YOU TOOK ADVANTAGE OF ME Brookmeyer, Bob, 5/1962 (Box 32A, Folder 14)
    BG No.: D424/276
  - YOU TOOK ADVANTAGE OF ME Karlin, Fred, 6/2/1960 (Box 32A, Folder 15)
    BG No.: D313/405
  - YOU TURNED THE TABLES ON ME Powell, Mel, 1947 (Box 32A, Folder 16)
    BG No.: C215
    Parts: cl/saxATBB/tpt/PGBD
    Note scoring for alto, tenor and two baritone saxes. Complete.
  - YOU TURNED THE TABLES ON ME Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 32A, Folder 17)
    BG No.: C215/132/y3/11/35
    SaxB, tpt4 and tbn3 are from another copy. Vocal arrangement, 76 measures.
  - YOU TURNED THE TABLES ON ME Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 32A, Folder 18)
    BG No.: C215/37
    Transposition from original by Bill Fontaine. Vocal arrangement. 41 measures (lacks opening band chorus).
  - YOU TURNED THE TABLES ON ME Williams, Mary Lou, 1948 (Box 32A, Folder 21)
    On the reverse side of all parts is an arrangement of "You Were Meant For Me".
  - YOU TURNED THE TABLES ON ME Burns, Ralph (Box 34, Folder 09)
  - YOU TURNED THE TABLES ON ME Mundy, Jimmy, 1936 (Box 32A, Folder 17A)
    BG No.: 35
    Parts: cl/saxAATT/tpt1-4/tbn1-2
    Recopy used in the 1980's. Rhythm parts used with this set found in preceding set of parts labeled BG. no.35. 76 measures.
  - YOU WAS RIGHT, BABY Henderson, Fletcher; Sampson, Edgar, 1945 (Box 32A, Folder 19)
    BG No.: 76A
  - YOU WENT TO MY HEAD Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 32A, Folder 20)
    BG No.: B321/16
  - YOU WERE MEANT FOR ME Williams, Mary Lou, 1948 (Box 32A, Folder 21)
    On the reverse side of all parts is an arrangement of "You Turned the Tables On Me".
  - YOU'D BE SO NICE TO COME HOME TO Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 32B, Folder 22)
    BG No.: C241/75A
    Parts: saxATTB(-A1)/tpt1-3/tbn1/G
  - YOU'LL NEVER KNOW Sauter, Eddie, 1942 (Box 32B, Folder 23)
    BG No.: C279/109A
    Parts: saxTB(-T2)/tpt1-3/tbn1/PGBD
  - YOU'LL NEVER KNOW, 1942 (Box 32B, Folder 24)
    BG No.: C279/78A
    Parts: saxAT(-A2T2)/tpt1-3/tbn1/PGBD
  - YOU'RE A HEAVENLY THING Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 32B, Folder 25)
    BG No.: B40/42/22
  - YOU'RE A SWEETHEART Henderson, Fletcher, 1937 (Box 32B, Folder 26)
    BG No.: D23/5/545B
    Parts: saxT(-T1)/tpt1/tbn1-2/PGD
  - YOU'RE ALWAYS THERE Byers, Billy, 1949 (Box 32B, Folder 27)
    BG No.: A264/813
  - YOU'RE ALWAYS THERE Valentine, Jerry, 1949 (Box 32B, Folder 28)
    BG No.: B325/252
    Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/PGBD/vocal
  - YOU'RE BLASE Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 32B, Folder 29)
    BG No.: 103/304E
    Parts: cl/saxATT(-A1)/tpt1,3/tbn1-3/PGB
  - YOU'RE BLASE Powell, Mel, 1948 (Box 32B, Folder 30)
    BG No.: 126
    Parts: cl2/saxT/tpt/PBDV
  - YOU'RE BREAKING MY HEART O'Farrill, Chico, 1949 (Box 32B, Folder 31)
    BG No.: A265
  - YOU'RE DRIVING ME CRAZY Henderson, Fletcher, 1938 (Box 32B, Folder 32)
    BG No.: A81
  - YOU'RE DRIVING ME CRAZY Jenkins, Gordon, 5/1976 (Box 32B, Folder 33)
    BG No.: G139
    Score: full and reduced (2 stave) marked "conductor/booth"
    Photocopies only of: tpt2-4/tbn2-4/PGB. Complete.
  - YOU'RE GONNA WAKE UP SOME DAY Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 32C, Folder 34)
    BG No.: A267/34
  - YOU'RE HERE, YOU'RE THERE Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 32C, Folder 35)
    BG No.: A268/232
  - YOU'RE IN LOVE WITH EVERYONE Mancini, Henry, 1942 (Box 32C, Folder 36)
    BG No.: D18/13A
    Parts: cl/saxATB(-A1T2)/tpt2/PBD
  - YOU'RE LONELY Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 32C, Folder 37)
    BG No.: A269
  - YOU'RE LOOKING FOR ROMANCE Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 32C, Folder 38)
    BG No.: A271/74
  - YOU'RE LOVELY MADAME Sampson, Edgar, 1938 (Box 32C, Folder 39)
    BG No.: A270
  - YOU'RE MINE YOU Sauter, Eddie, 1939 (Box 32C, Folder 40)
    BG No.: C41/9
    SaxB and tbn3 from a later copy.
  - YOU'RE MY DESIRE Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 32C, Folder 41)
    BG No.: A272/32
  - YOU'RE NOT FOOLING ANYONE BUT YOURSELF Sampson, Edgar, 4/1945 (Box 32C, Folder 42)
    BG No.: A273
  - YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY OYSTER IN THE STEW Lipman, Joe (Box 32C, Folder 43)
    BG No.: A63/90
  - YOU'VE GOT ME THIS WAY Henderson, Fletcher, 1941 (Box 32C, Folder 44)
    BG No.: A82
  - YOU, YOU DARLIN' Brooks, Dudley, 1940 (Box 32C, Folder 45)
    BG No.: 305
  - YOUNG IDEAS Henderson, Fletcher, 1935 (Box 32C, Folder 46)
    BG No.: A44/28
  - YOUR WORDS AND MY MUSIC Sauter, Eddie, 1941 (Box 32C, Folder 47)
    BG No.: B202
  - YOURS AND MINE Mundy, Jimmy, 1937 (Box 32D, Folder 48)
    BG No.: A279/20
  - YOURS IS MY HEART ALONE Henderson, Fletcher, 1939 (Box 32D, Folder 49)
    BG No.: A69
  - YOURS TRULY IS TRULY YOURS Henderson, Fletcher, 1936 (Box 32D, Folder 50)
    BG No.: A15/470/39
  - ZOOT SUIT Powell, Mel, 1942 (Box 32D, Folder 51)
    BG No.: A280
- Orchestral Arrangements
  - BACH GOES TO TOWN Brant, Henry (Box 35, Folder 01)
    BG No.: C249/B380/24E
    Parts: vl1-2/vla/vc
    "Special arrangement for the Budapest Quartet."
  - BEAUTIFUL LOVE Newsom, Tommy, 1/1963 (Box 35, Folder 02)
    BG No.: F15/21
    Parts: cl/saxAT/tpt/PBDV/vl1-2/vla/vc
  - BENNY SENT ME Sauter, Eddie (Box 35, Folder 03)
    BG No.: C244
    Parts: PGBDV/vl1-3/vla/ve
  - BEYOND THE SEA New, Paul, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 04)
    BG No.: A74
    Scored for: cl/fl/horn/strings/harp/celeste.
  - CAN'T WE BE FRIENDS (Box 35, Folder 05)
    BG No.: A349
    Parts: cl(2)/vl1(5)2(5)/vla(4)/vc(4)/B
    Clarinet parts in A and B flat. Complete.
  - COMANCHE WAR DANCE (Box 35, Folder 06)
    BG No.: C251
    Parts: saxAATT/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGBD/vl1-3
  - DARN THAT DREAM Sauter, Eddie, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 07)
    BG No.: A116/30/47/CapitallA
    Parts: cl/fl/horn/PGBD/vl1-3/vla/ve/harp
  - DIZZY FINGERS (Box 35, Folder 08)
    Parts: cl(2)/fl1-2/ob1-2/cl1-2/bsn1-2/horn1-4/PD1-2/vl1(3)2(3)3(2)4(2)/vla1-3/vc1-2/B(2)
    Also included are parts (BGno.343) for: saxATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-4. These parts have penciled rehearsal letters matching orchestra.
  - DIZZY FINGERS (Box 35, Folder 09)
    BG No.: D201/B
    Parts: cl/fl1-2/ob1-2/cl1-2/bsn1-2/horn13-24/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PD1(2)2/vl1(9)2(8)/vla(7)/vc(6)/B(5)/harp
  - DIZZY FINGERS (Box 35, Folder 10)
    Parts: fl1-2/ob1-2/cl1-2/bsn1-2/horn13-24/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/D1(2)2/vl1(9)2(9)/vla(7)/vc(6)/B(5)/harp
    This is a duplicate of BGno.D201/B.
  - DIZZY FINGERS (Box 35, Folder 11)
    BG No.: D201/A
    Parts: cl(2)/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-4/PGBDperc/horn1-4/tubavl(8)/vla(3)/vc(3)/B/harp
  - GERSHWIN ENCORE Newsom, Tommy (Box 35, Folder 12)
    Parts: cl/tpt(solo)/PGBDV/fl1-2/ob1-2/al1-2/bsn1-2/horn1-2/tpt1-2/Dtimp/vl(14)/vla(4)/vc(4)/B(2)
    Medley of: "Lady Be Good", "Love Walked In", "My Man's Gone", and "Strike Up The Band". First 3 tunes sextet only. Complete.
  - GERSHWIN MEDLEY NO. 1 Newsom, Tommy (Box 35, Folder 13)
    Parts: cl/tpt(solo)/fl1-2/ob1-2/cl1-2/bsn1-2/horn1-2/tpt1-2/PGBDV/timp/vl1(8)2(6)/vla(4)/vc(4)/B(5)
    "They All Laughed", "Nice Work If You Can Get It", "Soon", "Who Cares", "Summertime", and "Fascinatin' Rhythm". Complete.
  - GOODBYE (Box 35, Folder 14)
    BG No.: C337
    Parts: horn/vl1(8)2(8)/vla(4)/vc(5)/B(2)/harp
    Also includes transparencies of: vl1-2/vla/vc, marked A276.
  - GOODMAN MEDLEY #1 Knight, Peter, 1975 (Box 37, Folder --)
    Parts: scored for: cl/piccolo/fl1-3/ob1-3/enghn/cl1-3/bscl/bsn1-3/horn1-4/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/tuba/timp/perc/vl1-2/vla/vc/B/harp
    Medley of: "Poor Butterfly", "The Man I Love", "If I Had You", "Funny Valentine" and "Don't Be That Way". Four complete sets.
  - GOODMAN MEDLEY #2 Knight, Peter, 1975 (Box 37, Folder --)
    Parts: scored for: cl/fl1-3/ob1-2/cl1-2/bscl/bsn1-2/horn1-4/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/tuba/timp/perc/vl1-2/vla/vc/B/harp/celeste
    "Let's Dance", "Here's That Rainy Day", "I've Got You Under My Skin", "Send In The Clowns", etc. Three (plus) complete sets.
  - HENDERSON STOMP Spencer, Herbert (Box 35, Folder 15)
    BG No.: D212
    Score: full and condensed
    Parts: cl/fl1-3/ob1-2/enghn/cl/bsn1-3/horn1-4/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/tuba/D1-2("dance drums")/timp/vl1(10)2(10)/vla(9)/vc1(5)2(4)/B(7)
  - HORA STACCATO Alexander, Jeff (Box 35, Folder 16)
    Parts: saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/PGBD/vl1(3)2(3)3(3)/vla(3)/vc(3)/B(3)
  - I GOT A RIGHT TO SING THE BLUES Newsom, Tommy, 9/1964 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    BG No.: F107
    Parts: cl(2)/fl1-2/ob1-2/cl1-2/bsn1-2/horn1-4/GBperc/vl1(8)2(8)/vla(6)/vc(5)/B(3)
  - I ONLY HAVE EYES FOR YOU Wilkinson, Ralph (Box 36, Folder 01)
    BG No.: D202
    Parts: cl/fl1-2/ob1-2/cl1-2/bscl/bsn/horn13,24/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/tuba/Dperc/vl1(9)2(5)3(5)/vla(7)/vc(5)/B(6)/harp/P-celeste
    All string parts include original transparency. Also included is a full set of duplicate parts, lacking only solo cl. Complete.
  - INTERMEZZO (Box 36, Folder 02)
    BG No.: A332
    Score: full, condensed and two-stave
    Parts: cl/fl1-2/ob1-2/bsn1-2/horn13,24/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/tuba/D/timp/vl1(8)2(7)/vla(6)/vc(4)/B(4)/harp
    Also includes extra set of string parts. Complete.
  - L-O-V-E Newsom, Tommy, 9/1964 (Box 36, Folder 03)
    BG No.: F108
    Parts: cl(3)/piccolo/fl/ob1-2/cl1-2/bsn1-2/horn1-4/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/tuba/PGBDmarimba/vl1(8)2(8)/vla(6)/vc(5)/B(4)/harp
  - LAZY AFTERNOON Karlin, Fred, 1/15/1963 (Box 36, Folder 04)
    BG No.: F14
    Parts: tpt/PBD/vl1-2/vla/vc
    Trumpet feature. Complete.
  - LITTLE SHEPHERD Powell, Mel (Box 36, Folder 05)
    BG No.: E6
    Parts: cl/ob/horn/vl1(2)2(2)/vla/ve/B/harp
  - MORE THAN YOU KNOW (Box 36, Folder 06)
    Parts: cl1-4/fl/ob/horn/tpt1-3/tbn1-2/PGperc/vl1(5)2(6)3(4)/vla(5)/vc(4)/B(4)/harp
    Also includes transparencies of all string parts (6).
  - MY IDEAL (Box 36, Folder 07)
    BG No.: C356
    Parts: cl/fl/ob/cl1-2/bsn/horn/P/vl1(4)2(2)3(2)/vla(2)/vc(2)/B
  - SWING LOW SWEET CLARINET (Box 36, Folder 08)
    BG No.: D211
    Parts: cl(2)/cl1-2/bscl/horn/tpt1-4/tbn1-4/GBD/vl1(3)2(3)3(3)4(3)/vla(3)/vc/celeste/male choir
  - THREE PIECES (#1) Newsom, Tommy, 1/1963 (Box 36, Folder 09)
    BG No.: F18
    Parts: cl/vl1-2/vla/vc
  - THREE PIECES (#2) Newsom, Tommy, 1/1963 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    Parts: cl/tpt/PBD/vl1-2/vla/ve
  - THREE PIECES (#3) Newsom, Tommy, 1/1963 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    Parts: cl/saxT/tpt/PBD/vl1-2/vla/ve
  - UNTITLED (Box 36, Folder 12)
    BG No.: F131
    Scored for: cl/saxT/tpt/PGD/strings.
  - WISE-APPLE McBride, Robert, 1946 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    BG No.: E19/453
    Scored for: cl/strings.
- Swing Into Spring, April 9, 1958
  All instrumental arrangements, unless indicated, are by Ralph Burns. Vocal arrangements are by Buster Davis. The order below follows the sequence in which the arrangements were played, as listed in BG On The Record page 518. Arrangements held in the New York Public Library Benny Goodman Collection (JPB 80-37) are listed in sequence as well.
  In addition to those listed in this series, NYPL includes "The Human Thing To Do" and "Oh Baby" as part of Swing Into Spring. Neither arrangement is listed in BG On The Record.
  - Introduction
    NYPL, score and parts
    - OPENING - OLD (Box 33, Folder 1)
      Parts: cond-prod-P(3)/perc(3)/"vocal group"/vl4/vla4
      Includes incomplete transparencies for all parts.
    - OPENING - NEW (Box 33, Folder 2)
      Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/GBperc/vl(4)/vl-vc(4)/vocal group/harp
      Also includes transparencies for: cond-prod-P/vl/vla-vc/vocal group, and scratch sheet for revision of first five measures of "Opening - Old".
      N.B. There are two versions of this arrangement - old and new. The score and parts were not recopied for the new version, but simply altered. The final page of each part was re-made, and the old pages were kept. (They are stapled to the back of one of the old percussion parts.) New parts were made for the strings, "conductor production/piano", (abbreviated as cond-prod-P below) and for the vocal group.
    - RIDIN' HIGH (Box 33, Folder 3)
      Parts: cl/cond-prod-P
      The ending of this arrangement has been altered. There are two copies of the final page, each a different ending.
    - RIDIN' HIGH ENDING (Box 33, Folder 4)
      This arrangement featured Ella Fitzgerald. The vocal part includes music for both "Ridin' High" and "Ridin' High Ending".
    - STOMPIN' AT THE SAVOY (Box 33, Folder 5)
      Parts: cond-prod-P
      Transparencies only.
    - ROMANCE MEDLEY (Box 33, Folder 6)
      BG No.: 5
      Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/cond-prod-P/GBD
    - RACHEL'S DREAM (Box 33, Folder 7)
      Score: quintet only
      Parts: cond-prod-P/BD
    - BLUES MEDLEY Williams, George (Box 33, Folder 8)
      Medley of: "I Gotta Right To Sing The Blues", "Limehouse Blues", "How Come You Do Me Like You Do", "Poor Butterfly", "Hard-hearted Hannah", "I Got It Bad", and "St. Louis Blues". Also includes a transparency of a cond-prod-P part marked BGno.13, for a slightly different arrangement, possibly by Ralph Burns.
  - Blues Medley
    NYPL, parts only
    - CARELESS (Box 33, Folder 9)
      BG No.: 9
    - RADIO MEDLEY (Box 33, Folder 10)
      BG No.: 10
      Includes music for a new ending for the cond-prod-P part. Complete.
    - KING PORTER STOMP (Box 33, Folder 11)
      BG No.: 11
      Score: "new brass" only
      Parts: tpt(solo)/cond-prod-P
    - SPRING RHAPSODY (Box 33, Folder 12)
      BG No.: 14
      Parts: cl(3)/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/GB/vl(4)/vla-vc(4)/harp/perc(4)
      All clarinet parts are slightly different. Also includes transparencies for: vl/vla-vc/perc.
    - BLUE SKIES (Box 33, Folder 13)
      Parts: vl/vla-vc/perc(3)
    - I'D RATHER LEAD A BAND (Box 33, Folder 14)
      BG No.: 15A
      Parts: cond-prod-P/vla-ve
    - LET'S GET AWAY FROM IT ALL (TAG) (Box 33, Folder 15)
      Parts: vocal group-P
      Transparency only.
    - GOTTA BE THIS OR THAT (Box 33, Folder 16)
      BG No.: 17
      Score: in 3 parts (combination of "old" and "new")
      Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/cond-prod-P(3)/GBD
      All above parts are for a 167 measure unfinished version, except the cond-prod-P part, which is for a 128 measure arrangement marked "new". Also included is pp.3-12 of a cond-prod-P part that has been cut from 167 to 128 measures.
    - GOTTA BE THIS OR THAT XXX (Box 33, Folder 17)
      BG No.: A135/261/17
      Score: 6 measure tag only
      Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-4/tbn1-3/G(2)BD
      Also includes parts marked "Jo Stafford", "Red Norvo", "Harry James", and "Ella". Also transparencies of: cond-prod-P/vocal group-P. All parts include a 6 measure paste-in tag in A flat added 1/26/1974. These parts represent the final version used in Swing Into Spring. Refer to the full score included with the earlier version. The parts have been adapted to accommodate separate performance.
    - GOODBYE (Box 33, Folder 18)
      BG No.: 18/12
      Parts: cl/saxAATTB/tpt1-3/tbn1-3/GBD
    - CLOSING BILLBOARD (Box 33, Folder 19)